反恐24小时
第九季 第3集
前情提要
等等，怎麼回事？
Wait,what?
一等中尉
克里斯·坦纳
你們得馬上離開車輛！
You need to get away from that vehicle!
武器系统
我的無人機被什麼控制了！
Something's taken control of my drone!
不！
No!
問題一定出自我的操作密鑰
The answer has to be on that flight key.
我是被陷害的
Okay? I'm being set up
我對上帝發誓
I swear to God.
都別動！
Nobody move!
傑克，你幹嘛？
Jack, what are you doing?
兩周前我截獲一份情報
Two weeks ago, I intercepted intel
策劃刺殺海勒總統
framing an assassination plot on president Heller.
計劃就是今天，在倫敦這裏實施
It's supposed to take place in London here today.
情報裏面唯一能找到的名字
The only hard name I could pick out
就是德裏克·耶茨
was Derek yates.
我順藤摸瓜找到了他的組織
I tracked him to this organization.
也就是你這裏
Your organization.
黑客组织
是無人機
It's drones.
這個系統可以遠程控制多達十架美國無人機
This system can commandeer up to ten U.S. drones.
美军无人机造成四人死亡
有英国军人遇害
那是你幹的，對嗎？
This was you, yes?
是
Yep.
德里克·耶茨
過了今天
After today
末日時鐘的倒計只有一分鐘了
doomsday clock's set at one minute to.
世界末日？
End of the world?
美國總統
The American president
將在國外遇刺身亡
is gonna die on foreign soil.
一架美軍無人機在阿富汗向著
An fired a missile at one of our own
我們自己的戰鬥車輛發射了導彈
armored vehicles in Afghanistan.
死者裏面
Two of the dead
有兩名是英國軍官
were British officers.
正式提出要求
Make a formal request
讓我在議會上發言
to speak to parliament in session.
他們是老練嗜血的立法者
These are practiced legislators who want blood.
美国总统
詹姆斯·海勒
他們會叫您
They're gonna call you
殺人犯，場面會很難看
a murderer. It's brutal.
特別是對於一個
Especially for someone who
一個走下坡路的人
Who isn't at the top of their game.
你覺得
You don't think
办公厅主任
马克·布德罗
我不行了？
that I'm up to this?
你能說出另一位死於襲擊的
Can you name the other British soldier
英國士兵嗎？
killed in this attack?
他叫什麼名字？
What's his name?
你幹什麼，馬克
Damn it, Mark.
你不知道鮑爾對奧德莉做過什麼
You don't know what Bauer did to Audrey.
我陪伴了她三年，拯救了她
I stood by her for three years. Then I brought her back.
在她有生之年
As long as she lives
奥德莉
布德罗
她永遠不會聽到傑克·鮑爾這個名字
she'll never hear the name "Jack Bauer."
我可以辦到
I can do this, okay?
我可以找到鮑爾，我求你交給我去辦
I can find Bauer. I'm asking you to let me.
特工
凯特·摩根
我讓她復職了，讓她跟著你一起負責這事
I reinstated her. I'm putting her on this with you.
但你怎麼能指望我
But you don't really expect me to be working
我指望你做自己的事
I expect you to do your job
而不是質疑我的指令
without questioning my orders.
CIA分局局长
史蒂夫·纳瓦罗
我們得離開！
We're getting out of here.
耶茨，不許動！
Yates! Freeze!
鮑爾！
Bauer!
馬上放下武器
Put it down!
別讓他們跑了！
Don't let them go!
我在試圖阻止
I am trying to prevent
一起針對海勒總統的襲擊
an attack on president Heller.
而你妨礙我了
And you are getting in my way.
我想要你，現在就要
I want you, now.
可你總要等我方便完的啊
Actually, wait till I've finished, but...
是我，我拿到裝置了，但是有個問題
It's me. I've got the device, but there was a problem.
什麼問題？
What?
有人在追我們
Someone came after us.
你確定沒人跟著你？
Are you sure you're not being followed?
確定
Yes.
盡快回家
Come home as soon as you can.
媽咪在等你呢
Mummy's waiting.
以下事件发生在
下午13:00 至下午14:00 之间
-=TLF字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
就是這裏
There it is.
沃克斯豪爾格裏芬
The Vauxhall Griffin.
翻译  筱宸葭
好
Okay.
他們多久以前進去的？
How long ago did they enter?
基弗·萨瑟兰
不到十分鐘
Less than ten minutes.
好，把車停在後面
Okay, well, just pull around the back.
伊冯娜·斯特拉霍夫
盯著另一個入口
Cover the other entry.
翻译  lady5bird
泰特·多诺万
玛丽·莱恩·莱杰斯库
翻译  Jason Lee
威廉·德韦恩
格本加·阿金纳格贝
校对  诸星龟龟
馬上就來，先生
I'll be with you in a minute,mate.
謝謝
Thank you.
贾尔斯·马特蒂
统筹  饭离烨
特效  筱宸葭
迈克尔·温科特
本杰明·布拉特
基姆·瑞弗
客 串
米歇尔·费尔利
克羅伊，耶茨被殺了
Chloe, yates has been killed.
沒有掙扎的痕跡
No sign of a struggle
近距離下手的
up close and personal.
约翰·波耶加
罗斯·麦克科尔
手法很專業
A professional did this.
那個女的不在酒吧
Girl's no longer in the pub
所以要麼是她下的手
so she either double-crossed
要麼有其他人牽扯進來
or we got another player in this.
遙控裝置呢？
What about the override device?
沒看到
Not here.
有她離開酒吧的監控畫面嗎？
You got any visual image of her leaving the pub?
沒有，後門沒有監控系統
Negative. There's no cctv cameras at the back door.
媽的
Damn it.
我現在出去了
Okay, I'm on my way out.
沒有她離開酒吧的蹤跡
No signs of her leaving the pub.
埃米莉·伯林顿
利亚姆·加里根
克羅伊，她帶的假髮，她易容了
Chloe, she was wearing a wig. She's changed her appearance.
萨夏·达万
乔瑟夫·米尔森
米兰达·雷森
你要通過耶茨進酒吧時
You're gonna have to identify her by the case
帶的那個箱子來辨別她
that yates was carrying when he walked into the pub.
斯蒂芬·弗雷
這兒有個地鐵站，肯寧頓站
There's a subway stop, kennington station
在街對面
across the street.
檢查入口的監控攝像
Check the camera at the entrance.
傑克，看到她了
Jack, we got her.
她六分鐘前
She entered the tube station
進了地鐵站
six minutes ago.
裝置在她手上
She's carrying the device.
她上了地鐵北線
She boarded a train on the northern line
往北去了
heading north.
下一站是哪？
What's the next stop?
預計四分鐘後到達滑鐵盧站
Waterloo. Eta: Four minutes.
剪 辑
凯西·罗尔斯
我們得在三分鐘內趕到
We gotta make it in three.
艺术指导
乔纳森·李
沿著這裏，前面交通燈處左拐
Down here,make a left at the light.
摄 影
杰弗里 C·麦咖特
你們和這個人交過火
You exchanged gunfire with this man
他僱傭了你們這麼多人
he takes on how many of you
音 乐
肖恩·卡勒里
你們卻不知道他是誰？
but you have no idea who he is?
你被繩子勒傷了
That's a nasty rope burn.
是這個人幹的嗎？
This man do that to you?
制作人  金相圭
你現在皮下出血
I know you have subdermal hemorrhaging.
你的脖子會一直腫脹
The swelling's gonna continue until you're not
最後讓你不能呼吸
gonna be able to breathe anymore.
什麼？
What?
唐尼
Donny
告訴我這人是誰，來這裏幹什麼
Tell me who this man is and what he was doing here
制 作 人
伊恩·史密斯
我會給你找個醫生來，現在還來得及
and I'll get you to a doctor while there's still time.
他是來找耶茨的
He... he was here for yates.
唐尼，給我閉嘴，小子
Donny...Keep your mouth shut, son.
她玩你呢
She's playing you.
好吧，你是管事的
All right, you're in charge.
监 制
布莱恩·格雷泽
耶茨是誰？
Who's yates?
耶茨？他很暴力
Yates? He was violent...
瑞特
Ritter.
我們剛剛偵測到有人報警稱
We just detected calls coming into the local police
监 制
基弗·萨瑟兰
一夥武裝美國人在住宅區開槍
about armed Americans shooting up a housing project.
你和凱特在幹嘛？
What the hell are you and Kate doing?
我們差點抓到鮑爾
We almost had Bauer.
我們想查明他來此的原因
We're trying to find out why he was here.
你是說你們還在現場？
You telling me you're still on site?
是的，長官
Yes, sir.
趕緊離開
Get the hell out, now.
我們正處於外交危機中
We are in the middle of a diplomatic crisis.
你不會希望讓他們撞見
The last thing you need is
我們在英國的國土上開展行動吧
for the met to catch us running an op on British soil.
摩根特工還在盤問
Agent Morgan's still questioning
和鮑爾交火的人
the men Bauer was engaging.
對你而言，瑞特特工
As far as you're concerned, agent ritter
监 制
强·卡萨
凱特·摩根不在現場
Kate Morgan isn't there.
她甚至不在名單裏
She's not even on the books.
监 制
大卫·弗瑞
要是搞砸了，責任在你
This goes bad, it's on you.
給我們打開手銬
Uncuff us
监 制
罗伯特·科克伦
或許我們可以做個交易
and maybe we can discuss a deal.
只要你們說了耶茨是誰
We'll release you as soon as you tell me
為什麼這人要追他，就放了你們
who yates is and what this man wanted with him.
监 制
曼尼·科托
快點，別浪費我時間
Come on, stop wasting my time.
我不知道你是誰
I don't know who you are
监 制
伊万·卡茨
我也不關心
and I don't really care.
不過我知道
But what I do know
你們不是警察
is that you're not the police.
為什麼不給大家省點事
So why don't you both do us all a favor
馬上離開？
and piss off?
說啊
Go on.
监 制
霍华德·高登
凱特
Kate
编 剧
乔尔·苏尔诺
罗伯特·科克伦
當地警方馬上來了
Local police are on their way.
納瓦羅讓我們離開
Navarro wants us out.
我們不能走，這些人是追查鮑爾的唯一線索
We can't do that. These men are our only lead to Bauer.
编 剧
金相圭
帕特里克·萨默维尔
納瓦羅才不管這個
Navarro doesn't care.
給他們解開手銬，我們回去了
Cut 'em loose! We're leaving.
是，長官
Yes,sir.
不走運啊
Bad luck.
导 演
刁毓能
這個不解開
Leave him.
留下他
He stays.
你幹嘛？
What are you doing?
你瘋了嗎？
Are you out of your mind?
帶他回去，他知情
He's coming with us He knows something.
他根本
Well, he wasn't exactly
就不想開口
in a rush to speak, now, was he?
人人都有弱點，我們會找到他的弱點
Everybody has a weak spot. We'll find his.
納瓦羅讓我們離開
Navarro wants us out.
我們得趕緊走
We have to pull out.
納瓦羅還希望我們找到鮑爾
Navarro also wants us to find Bauer
所以抓住他的手
so grab his arms.
不
No.
那你還是走吧
Well,then, you better go.
因為我必須帶他走
Because I'm not leaving here without him.
你知道警方如果發現有CIA特工牽扯進來
Do you know what the police will do if they find
他們會怎麼做嗎？
CIA agents in the middle of this?
知道
Yeah.
滑鐵盧站到了
Now approaching Waterloo.
地鐵進站了
Train's coming in.
趕緊，我在地面街道跟著你
Hurry. I'll follow you on surface streets.
前往沃倫街的乘客請注意
Attention, passengers heading to Warren street.
第二軌道晚點
There is a delay on track two.
3點鐘的列車
Arrival time from the 3:00 track
會晚點10分鐘到達
will be delayed by ten minutes.
她在哪節車廂？
Which car is she on?
前面第五節
Fifth from the front.
借過
Excuse me.
下一站，查令十字站
Next stop, charing cross.
查令十字站到了
Now approaching Charing cross.
放下箱子，不然開槍了
Put the case down or I will shoot.
救命啊，這個人要殺我！
Help me! That man, he's trying to kill me!
她撒謊！
She's a liar!
救命啊！救命啊！
Help me! Help me!
放開那個女孩
Leave that girl a...
傑克，我到了
Jack, I'm here.
克羅伊，她往第二層去了
Chloe, she's made it to the second level.
能看到她嗎？
See if you can pick her up.
正在看
I'm looking.
克羅伊，看到她了吧
Chloe, tell me you got her.
她隨時可能出來，傑克
She should be coming out any second, Jack.
你在哪？
Come on... Where are you?
她一定是找到了其他出口，傑克，等一下
She must have found another exit, Jack. Hold on.
克羅伊，你看到她了嗎？
Chloe, you got her?
克羅伊，看到她了嗎？
Chloe, do you have her?
沒有，沒看到她
No. I don't see her.
跟丟了
I missed her.
你在哪？
Where are you?
查令十字站
I'm right in front
正前方
of charing cross station.
你跟丟了？怎麼會？
You missed her? How?
我就是跟丟了
I just did, okay?
你要我幫你找到耶茨，我們找到他了
You made me help you find yates. We found him.
他死了，所以讓我回去吧
He's dead. So just take me back.
克羅伊，你怎麼了？
Chloe, what the hell is going on?
我跟丟了她，是因為有一瞬間
I missed her because,for a second
我想我看到他們了
I-I thought I saw them.
看到誰？
Saw who?
莫裏斯和普萊斯考特
Morris and Prescott.
我愣住了
I froze.
我知道不可能是他們
I mean, obviously I knew it couldn't be them.
你不知道
You don't know.
知道什麼？
Know what?
他們死了
They're dead.
怎麼死的？
How?
練完足球後
Morris was driving Prescott
莫裏斯載普萊斯考特回家
home from soccer practice.
他們在交通燈處停下時
They stopped at a light
一輛卡車撞了過來
and a truck slammed into them.
天很黑
It was dark.
只有一個目擊者
And there was only one witness.
她只看到
And she just saw
一輛卡車開過
a truck driving away.
克羅伊
Chloe.
克羅伊，過來
Chloe, come here.
節哀順變
I am so sorry.
本來是我
I was the one.
一直都是我帶他去練足球
I was the one that always took him to soccer practice.
死的人本該是我
It was...It was supposed to be me.
但是那天我要加班
But I had to work late that night
所以我讓莫裏斯代我去
so I asked Morris to do it.
那個人本該是我，傑克
It was supposed to be me, Jack.
他們的目標是我
They were targeting me.
克羅伊，為什麼有人要加害於你？
Chloe, why would someone want to target you?
傑克，因為我知道你失蹤那天
Because, Jack,I know what happened
發生過什麼事
the day you disappeared.
人死不能復生
You can't bring back the ones you lost.
相信我
Trust me.
不過你可以用幫助其他人的方式來紀念他們
But you can honor their lives by  helping others.
這樣才能走出陰霾
It's the only way forward.
你可以無視海勒
You might not give a damn about Heller
但如果發生襲擊，無辜之人就會喪生
but if these attacks happen, innocent people will die.
很多很多
A lot of them.
克羅伊，我不想強迫你做什麼
Now, Chloe, I don't want to make you do anything.
但我需要你幫忙
But I need your help.
求你了
Please.
幫我阻止這些襲擊
Help me stop these attacks from happening.
什麼事，羅恩？
Yes, Ron?
我讀了這份關於
I looked into the protocol
引渡鮑爾去俄國的草案
of handing Bauer over to the Russians.
就算抓到他
Once we catch him
引渡也需要
rendition requires
總統的親自批准
the president's direct approval.
所以，我先起草了
So I went ahead and drafted
行政命令文件，但
the executive order, which
還要他簽字
He needs to sign.
謝了，羅恩，我會帶給他的
Thanks, Ron. I'll bring this to him.
但我們還得把這事盯緊點
But we need to keep a tight loop around this.
帶什麼給他？
Bring what to him?
我對你父親
My concerns about your father
把無人機操控員移交給英國這事
handing over the drone pilot
感到擔憂
to the British.
坦納中尉到達大使館後
Let me know when lieutenant Tanner
記得通知我
arrives at the embassy.
一定
Of course.
您好
Ma'am.
我過來是想和你談談
I was coming to talk to you.
你對我父親做得太過了
What you did to my father was cruel.
親愛的，我理解
Sweetheart, I understand
你的工作是幫他準備議會前的演講
Your job was to prep him for his speech before parliament.
而不是證明他講不好
Not prove that he's incapable of giving it.
比起其他議員，我並不過分
I was no harder on him than any member of parliament would be.
你讓他在我面前難堪
You humiliated him in front of me.
這就像，你是在為意見相左
It was like you were punishing the both of us
而懲罰我們
for-for-for disagreeing with you.
不是這樣的
That's not true.
他說了他可以的
He says he can do it.
或是他病得失去了判斷力？
Or is that his disease affecting his judgment?
聽著，即使你父親沒有
Look, even if your father wasn't
去妥協
in a... compromised state
試圖說服議會延長租期
it would be a fool's errand to try to convince parliament
也是愚蠢至極
to extend that lease.
他賭上了全部身家
He has staked his entire administration
來做這件事
on getting this done.
他能做到的，但不在這兒
And he will, but not here.
不是現在
Not now.
那什麼時候，怎麼做？
Then when and how?
我們回家，喘口氣
We go home, we take a beat.
再控制損害程度
We do damage control.
我們派些支持者，參加媒體運動
We send supporters on a media campaign
然後，再私下拉攏議員
and then we backchannel the mps we need to convert.
他不會買賬的
He won't go for it.
如果是你提出，他可能會
He might if it comes from you.
天啊
Oh, God.
聽著，親愛的，你父親
Look, honey, your father
還有政治資本
still has the political capital
來做成這件事
to make this happen.
但倘若他在議會面前丟了臉
But he will squander it, I promise you
一切就白費了
if he humiliates himself in front of parliament.
我會和他談談的
I'll talk to him.
謝謝
Thank you.
沒事
Yeah.
詹姆斯·海勒
美国总统
國際刑事警察組織人員
Looks like interpol
好像對她臉部做了定位，找到她了
has a facial rec match. We got her.
西蒙娜·阿爾哈拉茲
Simone Al-harazi.
通缉令
西蒙娜·阿尔哈拉兹
歐盟多次通緝的恐怖分子
Multiple eu warrants on terrorism-related charges.
等等，「阿爾哈拉茲」
Wait a second. "Al-harazi."
她和瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲有關係麼？
Is she related to margot Al-harazi?
通缉令
玛戈·阿尔哈拉兹
西蒙娜是她女兒
Simone is her daughter.
瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲
Margot Al-harazi.
約克郡人，喪偶
The Yorkshire widow.
第一任丈夫死時
Her first husband died
他們的兩個孩子只有三歲和五歲
when their two children were three and five.
她與基地頭目
She radicalized after she met
穆罕默德·阿爾哈拉茲結婚後
and married Al-qaeda commander.
變得激進，他們一起策劃了
Muhammad Al-harazi. They launched numerous
無數次襲擊，最著名的是
attacks together, most famously
開羅市集轟炸案
the Cairo Market bombing.
36名英國遊客死亡
36 English tourists died.
三年前，穆罕默德在美國無人機
Muhammad was killed in a U.S. drone strike
轟炸也門事件中喪生
in Yemen three years ago.
瑪戈同時遇襲，勉強倖存
Margot was with him. She barely survived.
三年前，那說明襲擊是海勒指示的
Three years ago,that means Heller authorized the attack.
該死
Damn it.
我們要回去找艾德裏安
We need to go back to Adrian.
發生什麼了？
What happened?
那個追耶茨的美國人在找我
The American who was after yates tracked me.
我逃走了
I got away.
但差點被抓
But just barely.
你也不知道這個美國人是誰？
And you have no idea who this American is
不知道他想幹什麼？
or what he wants?
不知道
No.
但你確信他沒跟過來？
But you're sure he didn't follow you?
是的
Yeah.
我確信
I'm sure.
給你
Here.
很好
Good.
歡迎回家
Welcome home.
嘿，老姐
Hey, sis.
你回來了
You're back.
給我吧
I'll take that.
怎麼了？
What?
耶茨用的非標準硬體總線
Yates has used a nonstandard hardware bus.
什麼意思？
Meaning?
上載之前
I'll have to conform it to our system
要與我們系統進行適配
before we get it online.
要多久？
How long?
不知道，一個小時？
I'm not sure. An hour?
可能更久
Maybe more.
快一點
Make it less.
唐宁街10号
鎖定目標了？
The targeting's done?
是的
It is.
我爱你
怎麼了？
What's wrong?
納維德，你像是剛吞了只耗子
Naveed, you look like you just swallowed a rat.
你三周都沒見過
You haven't seen your wife
你老婆了
in three weeks.
給她個好吻
Give her a proper kiss.
怎麼了？
What happened?
誰幹的？
Who did that to you?
把傷口清清
Get that wound cleaned up.
別讓它感染了
You don't want it getting infected.
我馬上過去
I'll be up in a minute.
納維德？
Naveed?
聽我說
Listen to me.
這事挺簡單
This is very simple.
我讓西蒙娜
What I asked Simone to do
與那個耶茨幹的事，是讓你反感
with this man yates is disgusting to you.
但你不能指責她
But you're wrong to blame her.
還有我，不能
Or me. Don't. No.
我不怪你
I-I don't blame you.
我丈夫常派我執行任務
My husband often sent me on operations
也需要我
which required my getting
接近別的男人
Close to other men.
但他常置之腦後
But he always got over it.
怎麼做到的？
How?
因為他明白
Because he understood
我只是做了應盡之責
I was only doing what needed to be done.
我們置身於戰爭，納維德
We are fighting a war, naveed.
最重要的是勝利
All that matters is winning.
西蒙娜做出了犧牲
Simone has made a sacrifice.
讓她做你的好妻子
Let her be a wife to you.
這對大家都好
It's what's best for everyone
對西蒙娜
Simone
對我
Me
也對你
You.
我一直在打你電話
I've been ringing you.
他們在追蹤我們手機
They were tracking our cell phones.
我們得把電話甩了
We had to dump them.
耶茨呢？
Yates-- where's he?
他掛了
He's dead.
你為什麼在這？我還以為我們兩清了
Why are you here? I thought we were done.
耶茨設計了一種可控十架
Yates designed an override device that can take control
美國無人機的遙控設備
of as many as ten U.S. drones.
這個設備，現在在一已知恐怖分子手上
That device is now in the hands of a known terrorist.
這些新型無人機，搭載六枚地獄火導彈
The new drones carry six hellfire missiles.
你知道這能對倫敦這樣的城市造成多大影響麼？
You have any idea what that could do to a city like London?
若你的國家沒有決定在空中
It wouldn't be an issue if your country hadn't decided
佈置這些重型武裝無人機
to fill the skies with unmanned
那這也就不會成為個問題吧？
heavily armed aircraft, would it?
你想怎樣？
What do you want?
既然找不到裝置
Since we can't find the device
我們就要證明裝置的存在
we need to prove that the device exists.
只要找到證據
As soon as I have that proof
我就上交政府
I'll deliver it to the government.
有人提過你有拿槍
Has anybody ever mentioned your rather rude habit
威脅人幫忙的野蠻行徑麼？
of asking for favors accompanied by the threat of a gun?
好了，我取得了
Here, I managed to get
遙控設備的
a partial screen grab
部分截圖
of the override device.
但不能證明坦納的無人機
It doesn't prove that Tanner's
是被劫持的
drone was hijacked.
而這正是關鍵之處，艾德裏安
That's what we need, Adrian.
你們恐怕得給我被劫無人機的
You'll have to get me the flight record of that drone
飛行數據，我才能找到證據
that was hijacked, I'm afraid, and there's your proof.
如果，它真是被劫持了
If, in fact, it was hijacked.
無人機的操控員叫坦納，新聞裏一直在說
The drone pilot's name is Tanner. It's all over the news.
他正被移交到英國方面進行調查
He's being handed over to the brits for their investigation.
飛行數據包含其中
The flight record will be part of that.
他們稱其為操作密鑰
They call it a flight key.
坦納現在在哪？
Where's Tanner now?
我從後門登入國務院服務器
I've backdoored into the state department servers
挖掘到了交叉口信息
data-mining signal traffic.
坦納即將到達美國駐倫敦大使館
Tanner's about to arrive at the U.S. embassy in London
進行交接
where the handover will take place.
找到證據後，我們只能
When we find the proof, we have to deliver it
上交給海勒總統一人
to president Heller and president Heller alone.
給我創建身份
I'm gonna need you to build me an identity
高級權限
high-level clearance.
加入大使館來訪登記
Enter it into the visitors log at the embassy.
要多久做好？
How quickly can you get that done?
如果我幫忙，會很快
Quickly, if I have help.
克羅斯先生
Mr. cross.
求你了
Please.
開工了
Let's do it.
克羅伊，我們需要大使館的圖示
Chloe, gonna need schematics
和一個無線通信裝置
of the embassy and a wireless comm unit.
收到
Copy.
我不管你們怎麼對我
I don't care what you do to me
因為我無可奉告，聽到了麼？
'cause I'm telling you nothing! Do you hear me?
我也不在乎你們是誰
And I don't care who you are.
前方隧道右轉
Make a right through that tunnel.
接下來幹嘛？水刑？
What now? Waterboarding?
你們在浪費時間
You're wasting yo time
因為我不會說的
'cause I ain't no grass.
就在這些門邊停車
We're gonna pull up here right by these doors.
我看了你的檔案，巴什爾
I took a look at your record, basher, and it seems
去年，你似乎和泰米爾人有些過節
that you had problem with the tamil boys last year.
海洛因交易中出千
Something about ripping them off
還殺了他們的人？
on a heroin deal and killing one of them?
不知道他們看開了沒？
I don't know. You think they've moved on?
去吧，巴什爾，滾出去
Go on, basher. Get out.
你也可以坐著
Or you can just wait here for them to come
等他們來把你請出去
and get you out of the car.
好吧，我全都告訴你
All right, I'll tell you what I know.
只要把車開走
Just drive the car.
我要先聽聽，說吧
I need to hear it first. Start talking.
耶茨在做些大的，需要人保護
Yates needed protection. He was working on something big.
關於無人機的
Something to do with drones.
無人機？
Drones?
是的
Yeah. Well
賣價可觀，就這些
the cash was massive. That's it.
誰是買家？
Who was paying him?
我不知道
I don't know.
這可行不通
That's not good enough.
聽著，我真不知道買家是誰
Look, I don't know who was paying him
但耶茨總在提及某個叫坦納的
but yates kept talking on about somebody named Tanner.
坦納？
Tanner?
是的，坦納，我就知道這些
That's it. Tanner. That's all I know.
快把車開走
Now, drive the car.
快開車！
Drive the car!
好，走吧
All right, let's go.
快開車！
Drive the car!
走，快走
Go, go, go.
快點！快開車！
Go! Drive it! Drive!
反对无人机
海勒是兇手！
Heller is a killer!
美国驻伦敦大使馆
海勒是兇手！
Heller is a killer!
如果他們知道是你
If they knew who you were
會把你碎屍萬段的
they'd tear you limb from limb.
我不該劃這麼深
I shouldn't have cut so deep.
嗯，就是隨便一劃
Mmm, you were improvising.
你覺得為什麼
How do you think
這個美國人要從耶茨的公寓
this American followed you
一路追你
from yates's flat
追到地鐵上？
To the tube?
我不知道
I don't know.
這真奇怪
It's strange.
也許
Maybe
是你大意了
You were careless.
他找不到這來
He can't find us here.
我們很安全
We're safe.
他找到你了
He found you.
我們有機會改寫歷史
We have the opportunity to change history.
憑借如此縝密的計劃
With a plan of this magnitude
不該有失誤的餘地
there is no margin for error.
根本沒有
None.
你絕不能放鬆警惕，西蒙娜
You can't ever let down your guard, Simone.
如果你覺得自己安全
If you think you're safe
提醒自己並非如此
remind yourself that you are not
無論你在哪裏
No matter where you are.
你懂的
Now, you know that.
我不是已經教過你了嗎？
I've taught you that already, haven't I?
你教過
You have.
很好
Good.
好多了
All better.
據國防部的說法，坦納聲稱有人控制了
According to dod, Tanner claims that somebody else took control
他的無人機，並開了火
of his drone and opened fire.
怎麼可能？
Is that even possible?
似乎國防部都不這麼認為
Dod doesn't seem to think so
他們還沒有證據支持坦納的說法
and they haven't found anything to support Tanner's claims.
肯定有什麼能把這些零碎線索串起來
There's something that makes all of these pieces fit together.
我們忽略了什麼呢？
What are we not seeing?
我不清楚
I don't know
但是我得承認，你很敏銳
but I got to admit, you're sharp.
敏銳到足以跟蹤鮑爾
Sharp enough to track Bauer
敏銳到讓巴什爾鬆口
sharp enough to get basher to talk.
如果你不介意我這麼說
Look, if you don't mind me saying
恕我直言，這令我納悶
and I mean no disrespect, it makes me wonder
你怎麼會沒弄清你丈夫當時所做的事情
how you missed what your husband was doing.
我每天都同樣捫心自問
I ask myself the same question every day.
是納瓦羅
It's navarro.
我是摩根
Morgan.
我剛剛盤問了你們戰術隊的成員們
I just debriefed members of your tac team.
你真的襲擊並綁架了一個英國公民嗎？
You actually assaulted and kidnapped a uk citizen?
長官，我有理由確信那人有情報
Sir, I had reason to believe the man had information
能帶我們找到鮑爾
that could lead us to Bauer.
我的命令是叫你馬上放棄任務
My orders were for you to immediately disengage.
那人給我們的信息可能與
The man gave us intel that may link Bauer
鮑爾和今早的無人機襲擊事件有關聯
to the drone attack this morning.
什麼樣的關聯？
What kind of link?
我們會認為鮑爾和無人機操控員合謀
Do we think that Bauer conspired with the drone pilot,
幫他策劃了這次攻擊？
helped him plan the attack?
還不清楚，但是我們正趕往大使館去盤問
We don't know, but we're heading to the embassy to question
該機操控員坦納中尉
the drone pilot, lieutenant Tanner.
好吧，去吧
All right, do it.
如果很難找到他就向我匯報
You let me know if you have any problem getting access to him.
有進一步的消息立刻聯繫我
Get back to me as soon as you know more.
遵命，長官
Yes, sir.
他同意了？
He's on board?
我和納瓦羅都很想搞清楚鮑爾這個人
Navarro wants to apprehend Bauer as much as I do.
我覺得那不可能
I didn't think that was possible.
美國大使館外示威者的數量
The number of demonstrators outside the American embassy
已暴增至三倍，之前有報告透露
has tripled since a report was leaked
克裏斯·坦納中尉
That lieutenant Christopher Tanner
請進
Come on in.
歸咎於來自友軍的誤射
Responsible for the friendly fire attack
正面臨內部隔離
was being sequestered inside.
爸爸？
Dad?
嘿
Hey.
這將是海勒總統首次向國會發表演講
This will be president Heller's first address to parliament
他們要血債血還
They want blood.
不知道他們想讓誰償還得更多些
I'm wondering whose they want more
是坦納中尉，還是我
lieutenant Tanner's or mine.
爸爸，我想跟你談一下
Dad, I want to talk to you
關於你去面見國會的事
about your appearance in front of parliament.
是馬克派你來說服我放棄的嗎？
Did Mark send you in here to try to talk me out of this?
搞不懂他怎麼會耽擱這麼久
I was wondering what the hell was taking him so long.
他關心這事
He's concerned.
我明白
I gather that.
我倆都關心
We both are.
要去面對一大幫
Going in front of a bunch
群情激憤的國會議員，可能會讓你
of angry mps might kill any chance
失去扳回一局的機會
that you still have to make this happen.
如果這種基本協議
If this base treaty
可以達成的話，在這裏也可以
is gonna happen, it's gonna happen here
此時此刻也可以
and it's gonna happen right now.
所以告訴你的丈夫
So you tell your husband
我感謝他的關心
That I appreciate his concern
但是談不成條件，我絕不回國
but I am not going home without that base.
我知道他
Look, I know that he
他有時好像控制欲強了些，但是
He can seem controlling at times, but
他只是在做他認為對的事
He's just doing what he thinks is best.
你和馬克相處得怎樣？
How are you and Mark getting along?
我們挺好
We're good.
挺好
Good.
所以，我還是讓你先穿好衣服吧
So, I'll-I'll let you, um, finish getting dressed.
反对无人机杀戮
克羅伊，我通行證的事進行得如何了？
Chloe, where are we at with my credentials?
大使館保安部門草木皆兵
Embassy security's gonna be on edge
這些示威者人多勢眾
with all these protesters.
正在進入大使館記錄
Inserting it into the embassy log now.
你能確定坦納的位置了嗎？
Have you been able to lock down a location on Tanner?
還沒有
Not yet.
我們已經確認了他的記錄
We've confirmed his records
在操作密鑰上
are on the flight key.
好樣的
Okay, good.
一旦找到他馬上回電我
Get back to me as soon as you find him.
收到
Copy.
你要麼示威，要麼滾蛋！
You're either with us or against us!
搞定
All right.
我進入了大使館來訪記錄
I'm in the embassy visitor log.
準備插入
Ready to insert this.
你真注意到那是個無效域代碼嗎？
You do realize that's not a valid field code?
這會使鮑爾被保安系統察覺的
It's gonna get Bauer flagged by security.
你會害他被抓的
You'll get him arrested.
你在幹嘛呢？
What are you doing?
媽媽要是知道你在喝酒會發脾氣的
My mother would be furious if she knew you were drinking.
你知道我愛你
You know I love you.
想過我沒？
Did you miss me?
現在不行
Not now.
來嘛
Come on.
我們說好了的
We talked about this.
你知道我得和耶茨做才能完成任務
You knew what I had to do with yates to get the job done.
我煩的不是這個
That's not what's bothering me.
那是什麼呢？
What is it, then?
我不知道我是否能這樣做
I don't know if I can do this.
我知道自己的任務
I knew what I signed up for
我也明白我們在這裏的任務
and I understand what we're trying to do here
但是我們越來越接近
but the closer and closer we get
昨晚我從惡夢中驚醒
Last night, I woke up from a nightmare
夢見我殺了所有這些人
where I killed all these people.
我看見婦女和兒童躺在街上
I saw women and children lying in the streets.
被風吹走
Blown away.
被火焚燒
Burnt.
沒事的，親愛的
It's okay, darling.
覺得害怕很正常，納維德
It is natural to be scared, naveed.
你覺得這些對我來說很輕鬆嗎？
You don't think this has been difficult for me as well?
殺人取命
It's no small thing
可不是小事
to kill a man.
眼睜睜看著他死去
To see the life go out of him.
我覺得我做不出這種事
I didn't think I could do it.
但確實是我幹的
But I did.
你也會如此
And so will you.
因為我們所做的一切都是必要而公正的
Because what we're doing is necessary and just.
你懂這道理
You know it is.
我們會共度難關的
We're gonna get through this together.
躺下吧
Just lie back.
總統閣下？
Mr. president?
移交飛行員
Handing over the pilot
也許能阻止少許流血衝突
may have stopped some of the bleeding for a bit
但今天早上的事件意味著
but this morning's incident means
很難爭取到贊成票來通過這項協議
that votes for this treaty are gonna be very hard to obtain.
他們會聽我的嗎？
Will they hear me out?
某些議員已經退出了，但，是的，他們會的
Well, some mps have walked out, but yes, they will.
但是我建議您不要發表演講
But I recommend you don't address them.
他們今天確實人多勢眾
They're a surly bunch today.
要扭轉他們的觀點實屬不易
It's gonna be a hell of a challenge to sway their minds.
這點我同意邱吉爾的話
I'm with Churchill on this one.
「樹立敵對方意味著」
"Having enemies means"
「你有自己的立場」
"you've stood up for something."
到底怎麼了？你說過
What happened? You said
你會說服他放棄的
you were gonna talk him out of it.
我努力了
I tried to.
奧德莉
Audrey
這並非我們說了算，是我父親做的決定
It's not our call. It's my father's.
你父親不適合做這個決定
Your father is in no condition to make that call.
但他認為他可以，而且你理應
Well, he thinks he is, and it's your job
支持他，馬克，你別再
to support him. Mark, you got to stop making
替他人做決定了
everyone's decisions for them.
你是這麼認為的嗎？
Is that what you think I do?
是啊，你也是這麼對我的，就好像你把我
Yeah, you do it to me, too. It's like you're keeping me
當易碎品一樣裝在盒子裏
in this little box like I'm some fragile keepsake.
我不知道，可能
I don't know, maybe it's a habit
你一如既往的照顧我是一種習慣
from all the time that you spent taking care of me
但是我再也不需要了
but I don't need that anymore.
房產會轉由政府接管
The house will move to government business.
請保持安靜，女士們，先生們
Call to order, ladies and gentlemen.
首相閣下，請您發言
Prime minister, you have the floor.
謝謝，議長先生
Thank you, Mr. speaker.
有鑒於今早的不幸事件
In the light of this morning's unfortunate events
海勒總統
president Heller
想要講幾句話
would like to offer some words.
有請美國總統
The president of the United States.
女士們，先生們
Ladies and gentlemen
你對今早的事件有何舉措？
What are you going to do about today's incident?
我希望有所言論來解釋所發生
I wish there were words that could explain what happened
當然有言論！
There are words!
這是謀殺！
It was murder!
你連自己的士兵和武器都管不了！
You can't control your soldiers or your weapons!
趕走無人機！
No more drones! No more drones!
上前一步
Step forward.
你的來訪事由？
Reason for your visit?
派送機密外交文件
Delivering classified diplomatic documents.
摘下墨鏡
Sunglasses.
抱歉
Sorry.
资料不匹配
有點問題
Something's not right.
有麻煩了
There's a problem.
到底怎麼回事？
What's going on?
所有信息都上傳到那個文件夾裏了
All the information was uploaded on that file.
艾德裏安說所有數據都查過了
Adrian says everything should check out.
證件有問題
The I.D.'S not working.
快離開，傑克，快
Get out of there, Jack. Get out.
不行，我必須進入大使館
I can't. I have to get into the embassy.
他跑了，召集人手
He's on the move. Call it in.
傑克，他們派保安來抓你
Jack, they're sending security after you.
給我站住！
Stop right there!
海勒是兇手！
Heller is a killer!
他們在朝我們開槍！
They're shooting at us!
他們在朝我們開槍！快走！
They're shooting at us! Go!
快走！快走！
Go! Go!
行動！
Move!
他們在朝我們開槍！
They're shooting at us!
快走！快走！
Move, move!
鮑爾！
Bauer!
更多原创翻译字幕请访问
TLF论坛：http://bbs.eastgame.org
TLF中文字幕站：http://sub.eastgame.org
TLF字幕组微博：http://weibo.com/tlfsubs